{
  "level": 3,
  "unit": 1,
  "vocabulary": [
    {
      "week": "12",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "___________ means looks up to something or someone very highly.",
          "answer": "admires"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ___________ is a person who is in the same class at school.",
          "answer": "classmate"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ___________ is a group of people who live in a certain area. They may share similar interests.",
          "answer": "community"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To ___________ means to supply, give, or bring something about.",
          "answer": "contribute"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "___________ means doing something over and over to gain skill.",
          "answer": "practicing"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To ___________ means to speak or say the sound of a letter or word.",
          "answer": "pronounce"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "___________ means to be afraid of or frightened by something.",
          "answer": "scared"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "___________ means suddenly fell in a helpless way or turned and rolled around.",
          "answer": "tumbled"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "34",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "When you ___________, you do something special.",
          "answer": "celebrate"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "___________ is bravery in a difficult situation.",
          "answer": "courage"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When something is a ___________, a person is sad because something is not as good as expected.",
          "answer": "disappointment"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Something is ___________ if it is very valuable to you.",
          "answer": "precious"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "___________ is a feeling of satisfaction in something you have done.",
          "answer": "pride"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When you ___________ someone, you make that person remember something.",
          "answer": "remind"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "You use ___________ to represent ideas or objects.",
          "answer": "symbols"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ___________ is something that has been done for a long time.",
          "answer": "tradition"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "5",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "A ___________ is an important building, large object, or place.",
          "answer": "carved"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A person who has ___________ something, cut it into a piece or shape.",
          "answer": "clues"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "___________ are hints that help someone find something or solve a mystery.",
          "answer": "grand"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "___________ means great, large, or magnificent.",
          "answer": "landmark"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Something that is ___________ is extremely large or heavy.",
          "answer": "massive"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ___________ is a building, statue, or object that honors a person or event.",
          "answer": "monument"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Something that is ___________ has a characteristic of or has to do with a nation or its government.",
          "answer": "national"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "___________ are small bits or signs left behind that show something was there.",
          "answer": "traces"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
